Guide to the Mary Sue Jones Papers
The Wittliff Collections
- New Mexico records, 1931-1992, undated
  - Personal, 1931-1992, undated
    - Divorce papers and correspondence with Roy Fridge, 1962-1964 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Family photos, clippings, mementos, 1964-1966 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Awards, photos, memorabilia, 1961-1992 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Preston Jones New Play Symposium, correspondence, press releases, 1984-1985 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Personal correspondence, programs, 1977-1983 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Personal correspondence, copy of speech made at New Mexico Repertory opening, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Personal correspondence, clippings, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Personal correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Address book, undated (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Clippings file, Gardening, includes hand-drawn garden design by Mary Sue Jones (Box 27, Folder 3-5)
    - Clippings file, Investments (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Clippings file, The Theater (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Clippings file, DTC (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Dallas Children's Theater, Board of Trustees meeting and budget information, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Clippings file, Preston Jones' plays (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Clippings file, Mary Sue Jones (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Clippings file, Paul Baker and Adrian Hall (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Clippings file, Fashion and Jewelry (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Clippings file, Health (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Clippings file, Automobiles (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Clippings file, Antiques/Crafts/Miscellaneous (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Clippings file, Travel (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Food mail-order catalogs (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Mail-order catalogs and clippings, lamps (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Clippings and catalogs, fabric and textiles (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Handwritten notes (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Articles from The New Yorker (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Clippings file, New Mexico (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Clippings file, Travel, Furniture, Appliances, and Real Estate Investment (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Clippings file, Pets, Career Information, research for Preston's plays (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Obituaries for Mary Sue Jones, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 12)